
var myFlashcards = [     {question:"Unless the steps of a method actually recite an order, not ordinarily construed to require one",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/interactive-gift.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>interactive gift</b></span></a>'},{question:"The corresponding structure for a function performed by a software algorithm is the algorithm itself. ",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/lighting-world-rodriguez-wms.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>WMS</b></span></a>'},{question:"during prosecution the PTO gives claims their 'broadest reasonable interpretation'.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/bigio-bigio-hyatt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bigio, hyatt</b></span></a>'},{question:"[C]laims are to be interpreted in light of the specification and with a view to ascertaining the invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/sebek-patel-sjolund-interval.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sjolund</b></span></a>'},{question:"PTO under no obligation to accept claim const. proffered as a prosecution history disclaimer",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/morris-tempo-lighting.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>morris, tempo lighting</b></span></a>'},{question:"Apparatus claims cover what a device is, not what a device does.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/hewlett-packard-schreiber.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hewlett-packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"Apparatus claims cover what a device is, not what a device does.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/hewlett-packard-schreiber.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hewlett-packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"evidence does not include dictionaries which only serve as aids to the court's understanding",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/nix-phillips-boon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nix, Phillips, boon</b></span></a>'},{question:"ordinary, simple English words, absent indication context changes meaning, mean exactly what they say",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/suitco-surface-chef-america.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>chef america</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI doesn't mean unfettered license to interpret claims to embrace anything remotely related.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/suitco-surface-chef-america.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>suitco surface</b></span></a>'},{question:"Every limitation positively recited in claim must be given effect to determine subject matter claim defines",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/wilder-enzo-lockwood.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wilder</b></span></a>'},{question:"the word "or" means that items in a sequence are alternatives to each other",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/schumer-medline.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schumer, medline</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim not limited to perf of steps in order recited, unless req explicit or implicit",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/antor-media-amgen-baldwin-graphic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>baldwin graphic, interactive gift</b></span></a>'},{question:"Preamble limiting when provides antecedent basis + nec to understand pos limit in body of claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/pacing-tech-beere.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>pacing tech, beere</b></span></a>'},{question:"optional elements do not narrow the claim because they can always be omitted",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/johnston.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>johnston</b></span></a>'},{question:"analyzed the linguistic precision of optional elements, must use permissive lang",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/johnston_10.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>johnston</b></span></a>'},{question:"when Spec specifies goal, any claim const. that renders invention incapable of meeting goal incorrect",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/rambus-lisle.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rambus, lisle</b></span></a>'},{question:"in response to' connotes second event occurs in reaction to first event ... automatically",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/am-calcar.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>am. calcar</b></span></a>'},{question:"free to recite apparatus features either structurally or functionally, but functionally carries a risk.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/schreiber.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schreiber</b></span></a>'},{question:"conjunctive interpretation of "or" is proper, phrase "`not A, B, or C' means `not A, not B, and not C.'"",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/vasudevan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>vasudevan</b></span></a>'},{question:"broadest reas interp ... does not include giving claims a legally incorrect interpretation.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/microsoft2-skvorecz-suitco-surface.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>microsoft2, skvorecz</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI not unfettered license to interpret claims to embrace anything remotely related to invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/microsoft2-skvorecz-suitco-surface.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>suitco surface</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim interpretation not so broad conflicts with meaning given to identical terms in analogous art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/cortright-skvorecz.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>cortright</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI during examination doesn't mean legally incorrect interpretation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/cortright-skvorecz.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Skvorecz</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI of a conditional step in a method claim includes instances in which conditional step would not be invoked",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/katz.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>katz</b></span></a>'},{question:"ordering of steps req when logic or grammar of claim lang or spec directly or implicitly req",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/minformation-taltech-wilder2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>minformation, TALtech</b></span></a>'},{question:"patentability of apparatus claim depends on claimed structure, not use or purpose of that structure.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/catalina-superior-industries-hewlett.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>catalina</b></span></a>'},{question:"improper to construe non-functional system claim terms making infringement/validity turn on function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/catalina-superior-industries-hewlett.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>paragon</b></span></a>'},{question:"machine inventor entitled to benefit of all uses, no matter whether he conceived idea of the use or not",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/catalina-superior-industries-hewlett.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>roberts</b></span></a>'},{question:"A system claim generally covers what the system is, not what the system does",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/catalina-superior-industries-hewlett.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>superior industries, hewlett-packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"novelty of the device used is not dispositive as to the patentability of method claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/k-2-rowe-catalina.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>catalina</b></span></a>'},{question:"functional or use limitations OK if describe structural requirements of device.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/k-2-rowe-catalina.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>K-2, Rowe</b></span></a>'},{question:"the PTO must give claims their broadest reasonable construction consistent with the specification.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/icon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ICON</b></span></a>'},{question:"It is immaterial whether similar claims have been allowed to others.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/gyurik-giolito.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>giolito</b></span></a>'},{question:"allowed claims in other apps or patents not considered in reviewing specific rejections of specific claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/gyurik-giolito.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gyurik</b></span></a>'},{question:"dep. claim that adds particular limitation gives rise to presumption limitation not present in ind. Claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/phillips-sunrace.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Phillips</b></span></a>'},{question:"presump of claim differentiation esp strong when limitation only meaningful diff between ind and dep claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/phillips-sunrace.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sunrace</b></span></a>'},{question:"if the method claim need not invoke conditional steps they need not be found in prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/katz-american-academy.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>katz, american academy</b></span></a>'},{question:"particu embodi in writ desc may not be read into claim when claim language broader than the embodiment.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/superguide.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>superguide</b></span></a>'},{question:"Claim differentiation means limitations stated in dependent claims not read into independent claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/nazomi-karlin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Nazomi, karlin</b></span></a>'},{question:"It is the patentability of the product claimed and not the recited process steps which must be established.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/brown.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>brown</b></span></a>'},{question:"When word of degree used fact-finder must determine if spec provides standard for measuring degree.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/seattle-box.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>seattle box</b></span></a>'},{question:"comprised of ok as other than "transition phrase," partakes of long-standing recognition as open-ended term",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/cias.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>CIAS</b></span></a>'},{question:"patentee may act as own lexicographer but must clearly express that intent in the written description",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/multiform-helmsderfer-brookhill-wilk.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>helmsderfer</b></span></a>'},{question:"special meaning for term must be clear in spec so any departure from common usage understood by POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/multiform-helmsderfer-brookhill-wilk.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>multiform</b></span></a>'},{question:"Absent express intent to impart novel meaning to claim term it takes ordinary and customary meaning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/multiform-helmsderfer-brookhill-wilk.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>brookhill-wilk</b></span></a>'},{question:"descriptive material must be functionally related to the substrate, to distinguish invention from prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/hotchkiss-boehringer-gulack.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gulack</b></span></a>'},{question:"classical 103 the knob of clay was simply the substitution of one [known] material for another [wood]",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/hotchkiss-boehringer-gulack.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hotchkiss</b></span></a>'},{question:"if "consisting of" appears in clause (a), not preamble, it limits only element set forth in clause (a)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/mannesmann.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mannesmann</b></span></a>'},{question:"complete invention in claim body + preamble only states intended use, not a claim limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/bell-comm-rowe-corning-glass-kropa.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>corning glass, kropa</b></span></a>'},{question:"where patentee uses preamble to recite structural limitations, PTO gives effect to that usage.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/bell-comm-rowe-corning-glass-kropa.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rowe, corning glass</b></span></a>'},{question:"[A] claim preamble has the import that the claim as a whole suggests for it.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/bell-comm-rowe-corning-glass-kropa.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bell comm</b></span></a>'},{question:"patentability may not be based on limitations not appearing in the claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/self-superguide-e-pass.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>self, superguide, e-pass</b></span></a>'},{question:"Where claim lists elements separately, implication is those elements are distinct components of invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/becton.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>becton</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI no unfettered license to interpret claims to embrace anything remotely related",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/abbott-diabetes-suitco-surface.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>abbott diabetes, suitco surface</b></span></a>'},{question:"optional elements do not narrow the claim because they can always be omitted",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/johnston.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>johnston</b></span></a>'},{question:"Claims may embrace different subject matter than is illustrated in the specific embodiments in the spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/phillips-sri.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>phillips</b></span></a>'},{question:"[i]t is the claims that measure the invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/phillips-sri.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>SRI</b></span></a>'},{question:"It is not function of the claims to specifically exclude possible inoperative substances",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/atlas-powder-dinh-nguyen.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>atlas powder, dinh-nguyen</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI must be consistent with ordinary meaning of term, use of term in spec and POSITA interpretation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/cortright-thorner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>cortright</b></span></a>'},{question:"To act as his own lexicographer, the patentee must clearly express an intent to redefine the term",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/cortright-thorner.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thorner</b></span></a>'},{question:""placed in an initial operating state" directed to user actions, not system capabilities",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/buysafe-ddr-holdings.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>katz, ultimatepointer</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble may provide claim const. context if intended use statement basis for distinguishing prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/metabolite.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>metabolite</b></span></a>'},{question:"wherein clause limiting if it provides "meaning and purpose to the manipulative steps" of the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/04/griffin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>griffin</b></span></a>'},{question:"apparatus claims cover what a device is, not what a device does.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/04/toshiba-hewlett-packard.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>toshiba, hewlett-packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"Negative claim limitations supported when specification describes reason to exclude relevant limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/04/santarus.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>santarus</b></span></a>'},{question:"rejecting an interpretation that renders a limitation meaninglessly empty",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/04/ethicon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ethicon</b></span></a>'},{question:"the Office may not read the claims in a way that would effectively expunge a term from the claim language",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/morris-k-2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>K-2</b></span></a>'},{question:"PTO applies to claim broadest reasonable meaning of words in ordinary usage as wld be understood by POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/morris-k-2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Morris</b></span></a>'},{question:"Expressions relating apparatus to contents during intended operation of no significance to patentability",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/thibault-otto.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thibault</b></span></a>'},{question:"one possible obvious combination falls outside claims fails to undercut other obvious combination lies within",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/acco.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ACCO</b></span></a>'},{question:"patentability of apparatus claims must depend upon structural limitations not upon statements of function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/michlin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>michlin</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble inot limiting if can be deleted and claim body describes structurally complete invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/american-medical.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>american medical</b></span></a>'},{question:"Without evidence of express intent to impart novel meaning to claim term, takes on ordinary meaning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/optical-disc.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>optical disc</b></span></a>'},{question:"When word of degree is used in claim, incumbent upon Appellants to provide standard for measuring it.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/seattle-box.html?spref=tw" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>seattle box</b></span></a>'},{question:"Whether preamble claim limitation determined on facts of each case in light of claim + invention described",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/06/tomtom-seattle-box.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>tomtom</b></span></a>'},{question:"rejecting claim construction that would render a claim term superfluous",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/06/mangosojt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mangosojt</b></span></a>'},{question:"the term 'substantially' in this context is used as a term of magnitude.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/epcon-deering.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>deering</b></span></a>'},{question:"the phrase 'substantially below' signifies language of magnitude",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/epcon-deering.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>epcon</b></span></a>'},{question:"broadest reasonable interpretation does not include giving claims a legally incorrect interpretation.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/skvorecz.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>skvorecz</b></span></a>'},{question:"All words in a claim must be considered in judging the patentability of that claim against the prior art.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/miller.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>miller</b></span></a>'},{question:"claiming broadly doesn't render claim insolubly ambiguous, nor prevent public from understanding the scope",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/smithkline-ultimax.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ultimax</b></span></a>'},{question:"Anticipation is a question of fact based on a preponderance of the evidence.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/baxter-travenol.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baxter travenol</b></span></a>'},{question:"It is well established that a human being cannot constitute a means within the scope of 112(6)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/voter-verified.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>voter verified</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble did not limit claim scope where it merely stated intended use or purpose of the invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/life-techs-hogan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>C.R. Bard</b></span></a>'},{question:"if statement of intended purpose constitutes limitation determined case by case in view of whole invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/stencel-cr-bard.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>stencel</b></span></a>'},{question:"Where result the same steps taken concurrently equivalent not patentable over steps taken successively",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/new-wrinkle-newell.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>new wrinkle</b></span></a>'},{question:"PTO's claim terms interpretation not so broad conflicts with meaning of identical terms in analogous art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/cortright.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>cortright</b></span></a>'},{question:"although spec often describes specific embodiments of invention can't confine claims to those embodiments",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/phillips.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Phillips</b></span></a>'},{question:"it is the claims that measure the invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/sri-cortright-brana.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>SRI</b></span></a>'},{question:"patentability is determined by the actual product made - not the process by which it is made",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/thorpe.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thorpe</b></span></a>'},{question:"claims were broader notwithstanding use of transitional phrase "consists of" because also used "comprising"",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/crish.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>crish</b></span></a>'},{question:"effect of preamble determined by reviewing entirety of the Appellants' disclosure",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/corning-glass.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>corning glass</b></span></a>'},{question:"informing a patient about the benefits of a drug in no way transforms process of taking the drug with food",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/king.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>king</b></span></a>'},{question:"When limitations in claim body rely upon the preamble, it may act as necessary component",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/contra-eaton-electro-sci.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>eaton, electro sci</b></span></a>'},{question:"in determining validity of a product-by-process claim focus is on product and not process of making it.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/greenliant.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>greenliant</b></span></a>'},{question:"harris - use of the term 'about' shows applicants did not intend to limit claimed ranges to their exact end-points",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/harris.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>harris</b></span></a>'},{question:"A claim interpretation that excludes preferred embodiment from scope of claim is rarely, if ever, correct",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/on-line-ahlert.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>on-line</b></span></a>'},{question:"invention disclosed in written desc may be outstanding in its field, but the name of the game is the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/hiniker.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hiniker</b></span></a>'},{question:"unreasonably broad const which doesn't reasonably reflect plain language + disclosure won't pass muster",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/ntp-cortright-suitco-surface-microsoft2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>microsoft2</b></span></a>'},{question:"A construction that is "unreasonably broad" and which doesn't reasonably reflect plain language + disclosure won't pass muster",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/ntp-cortright-suitco-surface-microsoft2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>NTP, cortright, suitco surface, microsoft2</b></span></a>'},{question:"When writ desc makes clear 'adapted to' has narrower meaning, the "adapted to" clause limits the claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/giannelli.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>giannelli</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim reqs ordering of steps when claim language reqs it or spec directly or implicitly reqs it",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/mformation.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mformation</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec may define claim terms by implication such that meaning may be ascertained by reading patent docs",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/mayo-diamond1-irdeto.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>irdeto</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI claim construction cannot be divorced from the specification and the record evidence.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/man-machine-ntp-microsoft2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>man machine, NTP</b></span></a>'},{question:"unreasonably broad construction which doesn't reasonably reflect plain lang in spec won't pass muster",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/man-machine-ntp-microsoft2.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>microsoft2</b></span></a>'},{question:"claimed functional lang assoc. with programming can't be ignored when applying prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/typhoon-microprocessor.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>typhoon, microprocessor</b></span></a>'},{question:"Where a claim lists elements separately, those elements are distinct components of the patented invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/becton.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Becton</b></span></a>'},{question:"construction that stays true to claim lang and naturally aligns with desc of inv correct construction",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/profectus.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>profectus</b></span></a>'},{question:"When different words or phrases are used in separate claims, a difference in meaning is presumed.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/nystrom-phillips-sunrace.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Nystrom</b></span></a>'},{question:"a dependent claim that adds a limitation gives rise to presumption it is not present in independent claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/nystrom-phillips-sunrace.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Phillips</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim differentiation esp strong when limitation only meaningful difference between indep and dep claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/nystrom-phillips-sunrace.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sunrace</b></span></a>'},{question:"the phrase "configured to" is narrower than "capable of" and has a meaning more akin to "designed to"",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/aspex.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>aspex</b></span></a>'},{question:"adapted to means "made to," "designed to," "configured to," more broadly "capable of," "suitable for"",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/man-machine.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>man machine</b></span></a>'},{question:"if preamble provides antecedence for ensuing claim terms limits the claim, giving life, meaning and vitality",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/kropa.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kropa</b></span></a>'},{question:"adapted to has narrower "configured to" meaning, req. elements designed to accomplish specified objective",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/aspex.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>aspex</b></span></a>'}
     ];

